{
    "1": {
      "question": "Which one of the following is a coding language also known as a term for coffee?\n(a) Java\n(b) Joe\n(c) CoffeeBean\n(d) None of the above\n",
      "answer": "a",
      "more_info": "Java was designed to have the look and feel of the C++ programming language, but is simpler to use and enforces an object-oriented programming model. Java can be used to create complete applications that may run on a single computer or be distributed among servers and clients in a network.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "Which was the world's first successful electronic computer?\n(a) PARAM\n(b) CRAY-1\n(c) Pascaline\n(d) ENIAC (Electronic Numerical Integrator And Computer)\n",
      "answer": "d",
      "more_info": "Electronic Numerical Integrator and Calculator was the first electronic general-purpose computer. It was Turing-complete, digital and able to solve 'a large class of numerical problems' through reprogramming.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "How is the quality of a printer measured?\n(a) Alphabet per strike\n(b) Words per Inch\n(c) Strike per Inch\n(d) Dots per Inch\n",
      "answer": "d",
      "more_info": "In printing, DPI (dots per inch) refers to the output resolution of a printer or imagesetter, and PPI (pixels per inch) refers to the input resolution of a photograph or image. DPI refers to the physical dot density of an image when it is reproduced as a real physical entity, for example printed onto paper.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "4": {
      "question": "Who developed Yahoo?\n(a) Dennis Ritchie & Ken Thompson\n(b) David Filo & Jerry Yang\n(c) Vint Cerf & Robert Kahn\n(d) Steve Case & Jeff Bezos\n",
      "answer": "b",
      "more_info": "Yahoo! was started at Stanford University. It was founded in January 1994 by Jerry Yang and David Filo, who were Electrical Engineering graduate students when they created a website named 'Jerry and David's Guide to the World Wide Web'. ",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "5": {
      "question": "Which is the latest version of Android?\n(a) Oreo\n(b) Nougat\n(c) Pie\n(d) Lollipop\n",
      "answer": "c",
      "more_info": "The Latest Version of Android is 9.0, Pie. The initial version of Android Pie (9.0) was released on August 6, 2018 on Pixel devices. ",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "6": {
      "question": "Which one was the first search engine on the internet\n(a) Google\n(b) Archie\n(c) Nemo\n(d) Intel\n",
      "answer": "b",
      "more_info": "One of the first search engines was archie(1990). Archie was a search engine designed specifically for indexing FTP archives. ",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "7": {
      "question": "Number of bit used by the IPv6 address\n(a) 32bit\n(b) 64bit\n(c) 128bit\n(d) 256bit\n",
      "answer": "c",
      "more_info": "IPv6 addresses are 128 bits long. ",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "8": {
      "question": "Which one is the first web browser invented in 1990\n(a) Internet Explorer\n(b) Mosaic\n(c) Mozilla Firefox\n(d) Nexus\n",
      "answer": "d",
      "more_info": "WorldWideWeb is the first web browser developed in 1990 in Objective-C. Later, WorldWideWeb was renamed to Nexus to make the difference to the World Wide Web clearer. ",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "9": {
      "question": "Which of the following is not an operating system\n(a) DOS\n(b) macOS\n(c) C\n(d) Linux\n",
      "answer": "c",
      "more_info": "C is a programming language and not an operating system. ",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "10": {
      "question": "1024 bit is equal to how many byte\n(a) 1Byte\n(b) 128Byte\n(c) 32Byte\n(d) 64Byte\n",
      "answer": "b",
      "more_info": "1024 bit are 128byte. Therefore is one byte eight bit. ",
      "user_response": "None"
    }
}  
